<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HockeyDJ</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="quickhelp">
        <![CDATA[<br><br><h1 style=\"text-align: center;\">Quick Help</h1><br><h3>No time to read? Watch our videos!</h3><ul><br><li><a title=\"Hockey DJ\" href=\"https://www.youtube.com/embed/hkHmH2cpHBM\">How to select playlists</a></li><br><li><a title=\"Hockey DJ\" href=\"https://www.youtube.com/embed/y8f2m8iVa5o\">How to delete or reset playlists</a></li><br><li><a title=\"Hockey DJ\" href=\"https://www.youtube.com/embed/xk6f7e_-YUo\">How to change the background</a></li><br></ul><br><p>The usage philosophy of the Hockey App is as follows.</p><br><h3>1 Step:</h3><p>Go to the music selection screens, marked with a music icon on the button of your device.</p><p>Define a playlist (a group of songs) to be played when a goal, a fault or a timeout of eachone of the teams or if a general interruption occurs during the game by selecting one of the options.</p><p>The second screen shows your music library, grouped either by playlist defined in itunes, or by album,artist or genre. This screen also shows in which places you have already selected songs for your playlist</p><p>The third screen allows you to select the songs for your playlist</p><br><h3>2 Step:</h3><p>After defining your playlists, go back to the main screen, marked by a hockey stick in the bottom of yourdevice. The buttons on the mainscreen should be now enabled.</p><p>By pressing one of the 7 buttons your device will start playing the corresponding playlist in randomorder. The first time you start a song, it might take one or two seconds to start playing. This is normaland is due to performing internal settings in your music library. Pressing the STOP button will stop the musicimmediately, pressing one of the 7 buttons will start another song of the corresponding playlist.</p><br><h3>Settings:</h3><p>You can set the background image of the app to show your favorite picture, or the logo of your favoriteteam. Set it to fill or fit the screen of your device and set the transparency of it to achieve best results.</p><p>For more information, please visit our homepage.</p><br><p>Enjoy using Hockey DJ!</p><br>]]>
    </string>
    <string name="acknowledgements">
        <![CDATA[<h1 style=\"text-align: center;\">Acknowledgements</h1><br><p>This application uses two free images from <a href=\"https://www.unsplash.com\">Unsplash.com</a>.</p><br><p>Hereby we want to thank the authors for these beautiful pictures:</p><br><p>Our startup image was photographed by:<br><a href=\"https://unsplash.com/@chrisliverani\">Chris Liverani</a></p><br><p>Our default image was photographed by:<br><a href=\"https://unsplash.com/@mroz\">Filip Mroz</a></p><br><p>Additionally, this application was possible thanks to the support of the guys at <a href=\"https://www.omalik.ch\">Omalik GmbH</a></p><br>]]>
    </string>
</resources>
